Guide to the C. Darwin Stolzenbach papers, 1930-1988 MS2028
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Director, IST [Institute for the Study of Transportation], 1968-1988; MS2028 Series 3; 1.5 Linear feet
  Newspaper clippings and articles are arranged chronologically; this is a small collection of contemporary news extracts. Notes, handwritten and typed, consist of written and typed notes taken by Stolzenbach related to telephone conversations, references, or ideas for chapters.
  Project proposals are arranged chronologically followed by undated material. These items are made up IST letters to various agencies describing the research to be undertaken. Project Reports are chronologically arranged, being reports generated by IST outlining project progress.
  Reports by other agencies are arranged alphabetically by name of agency. These include proposals to undertake research work for the IST.
  Mooney's manuscript is a good general reference to the history of Metro. This series contains little of a historical nature, but does serve to illustrate the workings of the IST and the state of Interstate and transportation-related history from 1984 to 1988.
  - Administrative Documents: Board of Directors, Agenda and Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Documents: Bylaws and Amendments, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Documents: IST Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Documents: IST Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Documents: IST Incorporation and Lease, 1984-1987 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Documents: IST Tax-Exempt Status, 1984 December (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Documents: IST Tax-Exempt Status, 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Documents: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Documents: Resumes and Biographies, Banks-Hunter, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Documents: Resumes and Biographies, Nehrt, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Documents: Resumes and Biographies, Patton, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Documents: Resumes and Biographies, Stolzenbach-Williams, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Booth Mooney's "Metro. Building Rapid Rail Transit in the National Capital Region" manuscript: Pages 1-42, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Booth Mooney's "Metro. Building Rapid Rail Transit in the National Capital Region" manuscript: Pages 43-97, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Booth Mooney's "Metro. Building Rapid Rail Transit in the National Capital Region" manuscript: Pages 98-144, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Booth Mooney's "Metro. Building Rapid Rail Transit in the National Capital Region" manuscript: Pages 145-200, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Booth Mooney's "Metro. Building Rapid Rail Transit in the National Capital Region" manuscript: Pages 201-240, appendices, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1979-1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Notes, Handwritten and Typed, 1979-1987 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Notes, Handwritten and Typed, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Notes, Handwritten and Typed, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Project Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Project Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Project Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Project Reports, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Reports by Other Agencies: American Association of State Highway and Transportation Officials, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Reports by Other Agencies: University of California to National Capital Transportation Agency, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Reports by Other Agencies: Transportation Executive Institute to Washington Scientific Services, Inc., undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous, 1950-1979; MS2028 Series 4; 18 Linear feet
  This series contains documents post-dating Stolzenbach's service as Administrator of the NCTA. Some of the material dates from the 1961-1965 period as well, such as in the cases of the Newspaper Clippings and Civil Action Suits. These were determined to be distinct collections in their own right and were thus kept intact.
  The Civil Action Suits materials are arranged chronologically by year the suit began and therein by suit number. Included are petitions, evidence, testimony, charges, and counter-suits for several famous and many less-famous Interstate-related civil suits brought against the Department of Transportation between 1960 and 1975.
  Legislation, post-1966 is arranged alphabetically by title, and follows the Legislation, pre-1966 material in the Administrator, NCTA series of bound and unbound official transcripts of Congressional proceedings.
  Miscellaneous materials are arranged alphabetically. Newspaper clippings are arranged chronologically. This items include clippings primarily from local papers related to transportation issues in the area.
  Oversize Reports, consisting of bound and printed reports, are organized by title. Public hearings, post-1966 are arranged by title and relate primarily to the hearings on the proposed 1-266 route.
  The reading files are organized alphabetically by name of the name of the person. Included are correspondence files generated by the various originators and apparently donated to Stolzenbach.
  Reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Included are bound and unbound reports generated by various authorities, primarily related to the WMATA and the Metro system.
  The material related to civil action suits contains complete, or nearly-complete, documentation of famous individual cases such as the Three Sisters Bridge case, and may be assumed to be one of the few complete collections of these documents.
  Newspaper clippings are the large and exhaustive group. They are valuable for their comprehensive coverage of general trends, issues, and concerns relating to highway development and mass transit.
  - Civil Action 2021-59, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 1172-63, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 3174-66, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 67-481, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 67-481, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 67-287, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 21416, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 21416, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 21416, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 21416, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 21416, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 21416, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1967-1973 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1967-1973 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1967-1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 23870, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 23870, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 23870, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 23870, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 23870, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 23870, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1967-1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1967-1973 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1967-1973 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 74-1974 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 23896, 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 71-931, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 24216, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 72-2103, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified Civil Action against the District of Columbia, et al, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action C-70-17, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action C-70-17, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action C-70-17, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action C-70-17, 1969-1971 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action C-70-17, 1969-1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 70-869-M, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 23574, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 23574, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 99-70, 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 99-70, 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 12030, 1967-1973 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 71-931, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 24838, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 24838, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Civil Actions, undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 24838, 1970-1971 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Civil Action, Arlington Coalition of Transportation vs. John Volpe, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Civil Action, Arlington Coalition of Transportation vs. John Volpe, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 69-295, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified Civil Action, Citizens to Preserve Overton Park vs. John Volpe, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Affidavits of Gerald P. Norton with Exhibits and Lowell K. Bridwell [Unidentified Civil Action], undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 99-70, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action 2821-69, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Civil Action 49053, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Advance Acquisition of Highway Rights-of-Way Study, 1967 July (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, 44th Street Case, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, Legislative History of the DC Appropriations, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, Legislative History of the DC Appropriations, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, Legislative History of the Dulles Metro, 1972 October (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, Legislative History of the Federal-Aid Highway Program, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, Legislative History of the Federal-Aid Highway Program, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Committee of 100, Legislative History of the Federal-Aid Highway Program, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Committee Print, Public Opinion in Washington DC Regarding New Freeways, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Committee Print, Report of the Joint Committee on Congressional Operations, 1972 September (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: DC Appropriations, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1968, Bills, Comments (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Federal-State Highway Management Practices and Procedures, 1968 May (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Fourteenth Street Highway Bridge, 1956 April-1966 May (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: "Hard Choices,", 1984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Hearings: Economic Analysis and the Efficiency of Government, 1970 May (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Hearings: The Interstate System in the District of Columbia, 1968 April (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Hearings: Major Highway Problems in DC, 1967 December (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Hearings: Revenue Proposals, 1968 April (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Hearings: Urban Highways, 1967 November (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: House of Representatives Report 91-463, DC Revenue Act of 1969 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Legislative History to Amend the National Capital Transportation Act of 1969, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Legislative History, DC Revenue 1971 and 1972, 1971-1972 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Morningside-Lenox Park Association, the "Atlanta Case,", 1967 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Natcher Hearings from DC Appropriations for 1969, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: National Capital Planning Act of 1952, undated (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: 1968 National Highway Needs Report, 1968 February (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: 1970 National Highway Needs Report, 1970 February (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: 1971 Report on Highway Relocation Assistance, 1971 April (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Public Space Utilization, 1967 October (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Report on the Status of the Federal-Aid Highway Program, 1970 April 15 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Second Supplemental Appropriation Bill, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: 23 USC Sec. 107, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Report to the Minneapolis Park Board, the "Minnesota Case,", undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: The Urban Mass Transportation Administration, undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: US Court of Appeals, DC Federation of Civic Associations vs. John Volpe, 1970 April (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Use of Air Space in the District of Columbia, 1967 July (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: WMATA, Legislation Relating to the Development of Rapid Transit in the Washington Metropolitan Area, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: WMATA, Legislation Relating to the Development of Rapid Transit in the Washington Metropolitan Area, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: post-1966, miscellaneous, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Chronology of WMATA [through 1976], undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Construction and information about Metro, 1977-1979 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Construction Contracts, 1964-1967 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Metro System College Directory, 1988-1989 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: National Archives Inventory of Record Group 328 records of the National Capital Planning Commission, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Potomac River Crossing, Contract, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles: Journal of the American Institute of Planners, Volume XXV Number 2, 1959 May (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles: David Young, "UMTA. Ten Years Later," MT, pages 10-16, 1968 September 10 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles: "When Highways and Cities Collide," City, 1967 July (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles: Bill Hogan, "The Day the Trolleys Stopped," Regardie's, pages 82-91, 1982 April 05 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles: Photocopy, "To stop highways, some citizens take to the streets," Smithsonian,pages 25-30, 1978 April (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles: "Pressures in the Process of Administrative Decsion. A Study of Highway Location," University of Pennsylvania Law Review, Volume 108, pages 534-576, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Magazine Articles, undated (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1962 December-1963 December (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1694 January-December (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 January-March (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 April-June (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 January-December (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 September-1967 January (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967 February-June (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967 July-December (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 January-March (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 April-May (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 June-August (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 September-December (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979 January-June (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)